Anders G. Nordby



Motzfeldtsgate 14, N-0187 Oslo, NORWAY (+47) 932 20 333 ■ anders@delichon.no

http://delichon.no/services/anders/
https://www.linkedin.com/in/agnordby/

DESCRIPTION

Anders is a project manager, systems architect and senior developer with customer focus and many years of experience in the industry. He holds the **PRINCE2 Practitioner**, **PRINCE2 Foundation** and **Certified Scrum Master** certifications, and he has also had the role of *team leader* and *scrum master* in several projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

05.2019 - PRESENT

Delichon AS

Systems Architect & Senior Developer

Roles: Daily Manager and currently the only employee.

Customers: ABB, Frank Resource Group.

Technologies: Azure DevOps, Akka.NET, TypeScript, React JS, C#, Microsoft .NET Core 2.2, ASP.NET Core MVC, Keycloak, TFS, Git.

01.2018 - 04.2019

Sopra Steria

Lead Software Engineer

Roles: In-house architect responsible for planning and QA of offers to customers. Senior developer for some customers.

Customers: Skatteetaten, Helsedirektoratet.

Technologies: C#, .Net, Episerver CMS, ASP.NET MVC, Microsoft SQL Server, JavaScript, Jira, Confluence, TFS, Git.

03.2014 - 08.2017

CGI

Senior Web Developer

Roles: Team-leder, scrum master, hands-on architect.

Customers: ASKO, Fellesforbundet, Tekna, PIA, Miljødirektoratet. **Technologies:** C#, .Net, inRiver PIM, Apptus eSales, Episerver CMS, Episerver Commerce, IdentityServer, T-SQL, WebAPI, NServiceBus, Jira, Confluence, jMeter, BlazeMeter, Angular.js, Knockout.js.

03.2014 - 08.2017

Making Waves / Tarantell Senior Systems Consultant

Roles: Senior developer and team leader in several customer projects. Customers: The Norwegian Government, Arcus, The Norwegian Board of Health Administration, Canal Digital Kabel, Synoptik, NMD. Technologies: C#, .Net, NewRelic, PowerShell, jQuery, PowerShell, Jira, Confluence, TFS, SubVersion

08.2008 – 12.2009	Creuna, Consultant / Systems Developer
02.2006 - 07.2008	Ocelluz, Systems Developer & Project Manager
10.2004 - 02.2008	Anders Nordby Konsulenttjenester
05.1995 – 06.2002	Ajilon, Consultant
08.1994 – 07.1995	Gran skole, Substitute Teacher

KEY COMPETENCIES

Processes

Systemarkitektur, Scrum, Kanban, prosjektledelse.

Development

Episerver CMS, Episerver Commerce, Episerver Find, C#, ASP.Net, MVC, Apptus eSales, inRiver PIM, IdentityServer, T-SQL, PL/SQL, JavaScript, JSON, Ajax, NServiceBus, WCF, WebServices, REST, WebAPI, XML, HTML, CSS, jQuery, PowerShell, LATEX.

Tools

Jira, Confluence, Git, TFS, SubVersion, ReSharper, NewRelic, jMeter, BlazeMeter, NuGet.

CERTIFICATIONS

2020	Microsoft Azure Fundamentals
2019	PRINCE2 Practitioner
2019	Certified Scrum Master
2019	Certified Episerver Developer
2018	PRINCE2 Foundation
2016	Certified inRiver Developer

COURSES

20	019	Iom Gilb: Architecture Workshop
20	810	Sopra Steria: Arkitekturskolen
20	015	Microsoft: Lead Enterprise Architect Programme

EDUCATION

0.11

4 1 ..

2003 – 2004	University of Oslo, Teacher Training
1999 – 2000	Oslo Business Academy, IT Candidate
1987 – 1996	University of Oslo, Cand.Mag.
1984 – 1987	Eikeli High School, Natural Sciences

AWARDS

2013-2017 Episerver Most Valued Professional

LANGUAGES

EXCELLENT	Norwegian (native), English
INTERMEDIATE	Bulgarian
BEGINNER	Spanish, German, Japanese